Mr Qin
Your left hand
That old injury
When did you get it
Can't remember
Sorry
Mr Qin
What's Fu Chenzhou's relationship with the Fu family
Mr Gu this isn't on the agenda
And it's none of the Gu family's business
Mr Lu
Can we pause the meeting for 10 minutes
Of course
Mr Fu can we speak in private
I'll wait for you outside
She's coming too
She's my wife
Oh
Of course
This is Fu Yanci
He is the grandson of the former
Fu Group chairman Fu Huaishan
He went missing 15 years ago
If you're willing
We can use standard procedures
To verify your identity
You can refuse
Or postpone it
The Fu family will respect your decision
The chairman has been looking for him for years